# Willie Newton

### **Broker Care Representative - Independence Blue Cross**

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Willie-Newton/1247a8cefb572cc8

Ability to establish priorities, accept responsibility, be it confidential and/or sensitive materials. Fast learner who can adapt to any situation and/or people quickly. A dedicated professional with drive, talent and initiative, always willing to go the extra mile. Strong cross-functional collaboration skills, strategic mindset, and ability to multitask, research and explore answers to provide alternative solutions if need be.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Broker Care Representative**

Independence Blue Cross - Spring Garden, PA - July 2014 to Present

Responsible for processing HIPPA Authorization forms, Enrollment Applications and 1095 IRS Tax forms in a timely fashion referencing IPDW Account Review

software, CIS software for viewing claims and Edifecs to determine accurate

information received from the Federally Funded Marketplace (i.e., enrollment

applications/updates of the insured is correct). Also access to AAA for broker and business related information, ROAM for brokerage site enrollment. Operate

Highmark software for Oscar, ICIS, CMRMAIN, ECS, PSAR, HIBS, EBILL, OCWA,

OPIS for documentation, benefit information, procedure pricing, Highbar billing,

enrollment verification/information, expenses members accrue as well as program availability for other insurance carriers.

#### **Customer Care Team Representative**

Whole Foods - Jenkintown, PA - June 2013 to July 2014

Monitor, clean, and proper maintenance on All refrigerant equipment on a daily

basis. Responsible for completing, and preparation of daily lists for staffing

assignments. Upheld all WFM and USDA standards including HACCP Program.

Established and executed food safety protocol, cleaning, and proper care (i.e.

knives, personal protective equipment, forklift, pallet jacks, hand trucks, six

wheel carts, and baler equipment used during preparation and clean up within department and facility).

Certified: Chemical Safety Training

#### **Administrative Sales Associate**

Radio Shack - Philadelphia, PA - June 2010 to June 2013

Managed store and its upkeep as well as opening/closing. Responsible for weekly

bank deposits, and handling Confidential credit checks. Training staff to detect

and/or prevent fraudulent sales/credit transactions and scams. Converse daily with potential buyers/customers training and certifying them on various

electronics. Overall understanding of multiple cellular companies, plans, policies in addition to hands on experience with the software to obtain members as new customers.

Able to work various shifts based on business needs, (i.e. evenings, holidays, weekends, call-outs and/or inclement weather).

1

338 Wellesley Road Philadelphia, PA 19119 267-456-3511 wjnewtoniv@yahoo.com

### **EDUCATION**

## **BA in Psychology**

Temple University 2014

## Diploma

Central High School - Philadelphia, PA 2010